

# **AJAY YADAV**

### Software Developer

I am a Software Developer with 2.5 years experience in development, I have a strong understanding of JavaScript and have worked on multiple framework like "React JS" and "Angular". I have also worked on backend technologies like "Node JS". I have hands on experience of working with "GitLab" and "Bit Bucket".

### **Contact**

(+91) 704 555 9387

yajay04112000@gmail.com

linkedin.com/ajay-yadav

**?** Thane - 421501

## **Technical Skills**

#### Professional-level:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React JS, Angular, Material UI, Bootstrap.

#### Moderate-level:

SQL, MySQL, Git & Gitlab, Node, Postman, Express JS.

#### Beginner-level;

Redux, Java, Spring Boot.

# **Education**

BSc Chemistry 2018-2022Chm CollegeCGPA - 9.5

HSC
 Fr. Agnel college
 Scored - 58%

SSC Bethel church school 2016 - 2017 Scored - 77%

# **Experience**

Software Developer
Krios Info Solutions Pvt Ltd

May 2024 - Present

- Worked on client's (Mahindra & Mahindra) FDW and Dealer Incentive projects as an Full-Stack Developer.
- Collaborated with team to provide deployments and builds.
- Followed proper coding standards and principles, Also maintained proper Git repositories.
- Provided KT on Angular and Git to colleagues.

### Software Developer

Immenso Tech Pvt Ltd

Jun 2023 - May 2024

- Created complex UI components in React and Angular implemented Reusable Components, Complex Logic.
- Created Restful APIs for business logic and integrated frontend, optimized SQL queries.
- I have also given multiple internal team Seminars Presentations on the topics like GIT, Angular, React, JavaScript etc. to the new team joiners.

### Software Developer

Sriyaan Technologies Pvt Ltd

Jun 2022 - May 2023

- Worked on the React project based on medical procedures booking CRM.
- Executed MySQL migrations by code to correct database records for any new feature added.
- Created test cases for modules & Changed verbiage in code & form validations etc.

# **Projects**

- (Mahindra & Mahindra)- FDW
- (Mahindra & Mahindra) Dealer Incentive
- (Immenso Tech) Rexi Portal
- (personal)-Stack Over Flow Clone(click\_here)
- (personal)-Image Gallery(click\_here)

## Language

English Hindi

